=Recruit A General to lead the Troops=
=تجنيد جنرال لقيادة القوات=
=Episode 17=
=الحلقة 17=
(County Office)
(مكتب المقاطعة)
Sir.
سيد.
Well, Mysterious Sir...
حسنًا، سيدي الغامض...
Mysterious Sir.
سيدي الغامض.
We couldn't find Dongfang Shan.
لم نتمكن من العثور على Dongfang Shan.
And Li Chengyu is still alive.
ولي تشنغيو لا يزال على قيد الحياة.
Li Chengyu is still alive?
هل لي تشنغيو لا يزال على قيد الحياة؟
And you couldn't locate Dongfang Shan?
ولم تتمكن من تحديد موقع دونغفانغ شان؟
What's the use of having you around?
ما الفائدة من وجودك حولي؟
Please have mercy on me, sir!
أرجوك أن ترحمني يا سيدي!
Please spare my life, Mysterious Sir!
أرجوك أن تنقذ حياتي، يا سيدي الغامض!
I bet you're almost recovered.
أراهن أنك تعافيت تقريبًا.
Your decoction is nothing but nourishing. I'm always energetic.
مشروبك مُغذّيٌّ للغاية. أنا دائمًا نشيط.
You're glib.
أنت لبق.
Xinrou.
شينرو.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
You've suffered these days.
لقد عانيت هذه الأيام.
I thought you weren't aware of that.
اعتقدت أنك لم تكن على علم بذلك.
You were forced to take in the other woman
لقد أُجبرت على قبول المرأة الأخرى
and put up with Liu Pitang's haughtiness.
وتحملت غطرسة ليو بيتانج.
Of course you'd feel wronged.
بالطبع سوف تشعر بالظلم.
(Above all, I actually suspected you were helping Chancellor to stage a rebellion.)
(فوق كل ذلك، كنت أشك في أنك تساعد المستشار في تنفيذ تمرد.)
I felt wronged
لقد شعرت بالظلم
not because of Dongfang Shan and Liu Pitang.
ليس بسبب دونغفانغ شان وليو بيتانغ.
I knew you took in Dongfang Shan due to the investigation.
لقد علمت أنك أخذت دونغفانغ شان بسبب التحقيق.
And I was aware Li Pitang's fate was beyond your control.
وكنت أعلم أن مصير لي بيتانج كان خارج سيطرتك.
It's just that...
إنه فقط ذلك...
It's just that you never told me anything.
فقط أنك لم تخبرني بأي شيء أبدًا.
It's complicated.
إنه أمر معقد.
Once everything is over,
بمجرد أن ينتهي كل شيء،
I'll tell you about it.
سأخبرك عن ذلك.
Well, promise me,
حسنا، وعدني،
don't do Qingfeng Stronghold harm no matter what.
لا تسبب أي ضرر لقلعة تشينغفينغ مهما كان الأمر.
Don't
لا
hurt yourself too.
أذي نفسك أيضًا.
Sure, you have my word.
بالتأكيد، لديك كلمتي.
General Li.
الجنرال لي.
Try this liquor.
جرب هذا المشروب.
(Liquor) It's definitely a nice one.
(مشروب كحولي) إنه بالتأكيد لطيف.
What an unexpected visit, County Magistrate.
يا لها من زيارة غير متوقعة، يا قاضي المقاطعة.
Why? Are you here to mess with me?
لماذا؟ هل أنت هنا لتعبث معي؟
You're jesting.
أنت تمزح.
At first, I really had no idea you're a general.
في البداية، لم يكن لدي أي فكرة أنك جنرال.
Pardon me for that.
عذرا على ذلك.
You're also the owner of a resort.
أنت أيضًا مالك المنتجع.
There are opportunities for us to collaborate after this.
هناك فرص لنا للتعاون بعد ذلك.
Let's get rich together.
دعونا نصبح أغنياء معًا.
You felt sorry for not knowing that I'm a general.
لقد شعرت بالأسف لعدم معرفتك بأنني جنرال.
Yet you had Liu go to Qingfeng Stronghold to catch me two days ago.
ومع ذلك، فقد طلبت من ليو أن يذهب إلى معقل تشينغفينغ ليقبض علي قبل يومين.
That's a double standard.
هذا هو معيار مزدوج.
That wasn't my idea.
لم تكن هذه فكرتي.
Don't... Don't get me wrong.
لا... لا تفهمني خطأ.
I just helped Liu
لقد ساعدت ليو للتو
to take over Mr. Qian's winery.
لتولي إدارة مصنع النبيذ الخاص بالسيد تشيان.
I was trying to gain something out of that.
كنت أحاول الحصول على شيء من ذلك.
Oh my!
يا إلهي!
Who would have thought he'd be an ingrate by turning against you
من كان يظن أنه سيكون جاحدًا للجميل بالانقلاب عليك؟
and sowing discord among us?
وإثارة الفتنة بيننا؟
He really deserves death!
إنه يستحق الموت فعلاً!
He does deserve death.
إنه يستحق الموت.
Where's his body?
أين جثته؟
Well, don't worry.
حسنًا، لا تقلق.
I've had my men search the entire city.
لقد طلبت من رجالي البحث في المدينة بأكملها.
I will give you a satisfactory answer.
سأعطيك جوابا مرضيا.
Today, not only am I here to apologize to you,
اليوم، أنا لست هنا فقط للاعتذار لك،
but I'd also like to ask you for a favor.
ولكنني أود أيضًا أن أطلب منك معروفًا.
The prefectural magistrate
قاضي المحافظة
is visiting this small town soon.
سيقوم بزيارة هذه المدينة الصغيرة قريبًا.
And he'd like to hold a banquet
ويريد أن يقيم مأدبة
at some unique inn.
في بعض النزل الفريدة من نوعها.
Having given it a thought,
بعد أن فكرت في الأمر،
I think our holiday resort is the most unique of all.
أعتقد أن منتجعنا السياحي هو الأكثر تميزًا على الإطلاق.
You need the support of these local officials
أنت بحاجة إلى دعم هؤلاء المسؤولين المحليين
to make your business bloom.
لتجعل عملك يزدهر.
Since you hold a high position,
بما أنك تشغل منصبًا عاليًا،
naturally, you have no idea about the way of survival here.
بطبيعة الحال، ليس لديك أي فكرة عن طريقة البقاء على قيد الحياة هنا.
Suit yourself.
تناسب نفسك.
I'm done eating. Please excuse me.
لقد انتهيت من الأكل. أرجو المعذرة.
And take back that stupid liquor of yours.
وخذ هذا المشروب الغبي منك.
That's great news!
هذه اخبار رائعة!
You shouldn't say no to it.
لا ينبغي عليك أن تقول لا لذلك.
If the prefectural magistrate has a high praise of it,
إذا كان لدى قاضي المحافظة ثناء كبير عليه،
our business will prosper for sure.
أعمالنا سوف تزدهر بالتأكيد.
I think that cunning official is up to no good.
أعتقد أن هذا المسؤول الماكر لا يفعل شيئا جيدا.
Well, if he's cunning,
حسنًا، إذا كان ماكرًا،
he'll just order you
سوف يأمرك فقط
to give him a special banquet.
ليقيم له وليمة خاصة.
Solve that issue
حل هذه المشكلة
and he won't find fault with you.
ولن يجد فيك عيبا.
I don't think that'll work.
لا أعتقد أن هذا سينجح.
My goodness. Go ask Manyue.
يا إلهي، اذهب واسأل مانيو.
She's full of peculiar ideas.
إنها مليئة بالأفكار الغريبة.
Go on.
إستمر.
Fine.
بخير.
Didn't I forbid you to send letters?
ألم أنهاك عن إرسال الرسائل؟
I only listen to Minister Li.
أنا فقط أستمع إلى الوزير لي.
I'll explain myself to him.
سأشرح له نفسي.
You'd ruin my plan.
سوف تدمر خطتي.
Besides, do you think I'll do you harm?
وبالإضافة إلى ذلك، هل تعتقد أنني سوف أؤذيك؟
Isn't Minister Li your brother?
أليس الوزير لي أخاك؟
What's the big deal with sending him a letter?
ما المشكلة في إرسال رسالة له؟
I see, Minister Li is Li Aotian.
أرى أن الوزير لي هو لي أوتيان.
Who else could it be?
من يمكن أن يكون غيره؟
You do listen to him, huh?
أنت تستمع إليه، أليس كذلك؟
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدا،
I only do as Minister Li says.
أنا أفعل فقط ما يقوله الوزير لي.
Back then, my father was a trivial official in the capital.
في ذلك الوقت كان والدي موظفاً عادياً في العاصمة.
He made a reckless mistake,
لقد ارتكب خطأ متهورًا،
(and our family ended up in jail.)
(وانتهى الأمر بعائلتنا في السجن.)
Someone paid to have your life taken!
لقد دفع أحدهم من أجل أن يُسلب حياتك!
(Someone was jealous of my father because of his influential status.)
(كان أحدهم يغار من والدي بسبب نفوذه.)
(So they wanted to kill us all in jail.)
(لذلك أرادوا قتلنا جميعًا في السجن.)
(Minister Li took that blow)
(الوزير لي تلقى تلك الضربة)
(and saved my life.)
(و أنقذت حياتي.)
Guards.
حراس.
Get these bodies out of here!
أخرجوا هذه الجثث من هنا!
If it weren't for him, I would've...
لو لم يكن هو لفعلت...
Do you fancy him?
هل أنت معجب به؟
Well, does he know you like him?
حسنًا، هل يعرف أنك تحبينه؟
Minister Li is always occupied.
الوزير لي مشغول دائمًا.
He doesn't have time for me.
ليس لديه وقت لي.
Come on, it's all right.
هيا، كل شيء على ما يرام.
To my surprise, you're lovesick.
لمفاجأتي، أنت مريض بالحب.
Fine. If there's a chance, I'll matchmake you two.
حسناً. إذا سنحت الفرصة، سأختاركما.
Just buy me a meal when you're together.
فقط اشتري لي وجبة طعام عندما تكونان معًا.
I have an idea about the banquet.
لدي فكرة عن المأدبة.
Is this the surprise you got me, County Magistrate?
هل هذه هي المفاجأة التي فاجئتني بها، يا قاضي المقاطعة؟
Sir.
سيد.
Pardon me...
اعذرني...
Perhaps Mr. Li has forgotten about the banquet
ربما نسي السيد لي أمر المأدبة
due to his busy schedule.
بسبب جدول أعماله المزدحم.
Gosh, I'm not here for mountain climbing.
يا إلهي، أنا لست هنا لتسلق الجبال.
With your incompetence,
مع عدم كفاءتك،
you might as well resign and do pig farming.
قد يكون من الأفضل أن تستقيل وتعمل في تربية الخنازير.
My God! Please calm down, sir!
يا إلهي! اهدأ يا سيدي!
Let me check on it.
دعني أتحقق من ذلك.
(House of Joy)
(بيت الفرح)
Mr. Li.
السيد لي.
Have you forgotten about
هل نسيت؟
the prefectural magistrate's banquet here?
مأدبة قاضي المقاطعة هنا؟
Prefectural Magistrate.
قاضي المحافظة.
Patient.
مريض.
I've got you a surprise in there.
لقد أعددت لك مفاجأة هناك.
Come, let's go check it out.
تعال، دعنا نذهب للتحقق من ذلك.
Please.
لو سمحت.
This way, please, sir.
من هنا، من فضلك، سيدي.
Ready, go!
جاهز، اذهب!
Welcome!
مرحباً!
Isn't this a bathhouse?
أليس هذا حماما؟
There's nothing special about it.
لا يوجد شيء خاص فيه.
Prefectural Magistrate.
قاضي المحافظة.
This is no ordinary official banquet.
هذا ليس مأدبة رسمية عادية.
The highlight is the hot springs here.
أهم ما يميز هذا المكان هو الينابيع الساخنة.
You get to have a foot soak
يمكنك الحصول على نقع القدمين
while enjoying delicious food.
بينما تستمتع بالطعام اللذيذ.
Wouldn't that be wonderful?
ألا سيكون ذلك رائعا؟
Doesn't that sound interesting?
ألا يبدو هذا مثيرا للاهتمام؟
Well, that sounds great.
حسنًا، هذا يبدو رائعًا.
Nice one!
هذا لطيف!
Visit this place often and you'll find it fun.
قم بزيارة هذا المكان كثيرًا وستجده ممتعًا.
I too find that interesting.
أجد ذلك مثيرا للاهتمام أيضًا.
Well, please be seated.
حسنًا، يرجى الجلوس.
Don't just stand here.
لا تقف هنا فقط.
Chengyu.
تشنغيو.
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Let's go...
دعنا نذهب...
Help!
يساعد!
Prefectural Magistrate.
قاضي المحافظة.
Come here!
تعال الى هنا!
Look!
ينظر!
There's a body in the hot spring.
هناك جثة في الينابيع الساخنة.
Li Chengyu.
لي تشينجيو.
You've really got me a big surprise!
لقد فاجئتني حقا!
Sir.
سيد.
The County Office received a report not long ago.
وقد تلقى مكتب المقاطعة تقريرًا منذ فترة ليست طويلة.
They said Li Chengyu forcibly brought Dongfang Shan here to the mountain.
قالوا أن لي تشنغيو أحضر دونغفانغ شان بالقوة إلى هنا إلى الجبل.
She was nowhere to be seen since then.
ولم تعد موجودة في أي مكان منذ ذلك الحين.
I also heard
سمعت أيضا
that Li Chengyu tied the knot with Dongfang Shan
أن لي تشنغيو عقد قرانه على دونغفانغ شان
in front
أمام
of everyone.
من الجميع.
I've got it figured out
لقد فهمت الأمر
now that I'm here.
الآن بعد أن أصبحت هنا.
He tricked Dongfang Shan into coming here
لقد خدع دونغفانغ شان ليأتي إلى هنا
and got rid of her!
وتخلصت منها!
Stop feigning ignorance!
توقف عن التظاهر بالجهل!
They may not know what caused Dongfang Shan's death,
قد لا يعرفون سبب وفاة دونغفانغ شان،
but I do!
ولكنني افعل ذلك!
Say something!
قل شيئا!
I'm the county magistrate.
أنا قاضي المقاطعة.
Stop it, Li Chengyu!
توقف عن ذلك، لي تشينجيو!
You killed this lady here.
لقد قتلت هذه السيدة هنا.
Are you going to kill an imperial official
هل ستقتل مسؤولا إمبراطوريا؟
in front of us all?
أمامنا جميعا؟
County magistrate, my foot!
قاضي المقاطعة، قدمي!
You're going against my order here.
أنت تخالف أمري هنا.
How lawless of you!
كم أنت خارج عن القانون!
What are you waiting for?
ماذا تنتظر؟
Catch this murderer!
قبض على هذا القاتل!
Chengyu!
تشنغيو!
Cold Tiger!
النمر البارد!
Don't kill him!
لا تقتله!
This has nothing to do with you.
ليس لهذا علاقة بك .
I killed her.
لقد قتلتها.
I did!
فعلتُ!
Just catch me.
فقط امسكني.
Arrest me.
إعتقلوني.
- What are you doing, Cold Tiger? - Chengyu.
- ماذا تفعل أيها النمر البارد؟ - تشنغيو.
This woman was being disobedient,
كانت هذه المرأة عاصية،
so I killed her.
لذلك قتلتها.
I threw the body into the water.
رميت الجثة في الماء.
But I never thought it'd float.
ولكنني لم أتوقع أبدًا أن يطفو.
I killed her.
لقد قتلتها.
I did that.
لقد فعلت ذلك.
Just catch me.
فقط امسكني.
Here, arrest him.
هنا، القبض عليه.
As long as I'm around,
طالما أنا موجود،
no one can catch him!
لا أحد يستطيع الإمساك به!
This is a trap, Chengyu.
هذا فخ، تشنغيو.
Don't fall for it.
لا تنخدع بذلك.
Chengyu.
تشنغيو.
They won't stop until they get one of us.
لن يتوقفوا حتى يقبضوا على أحدنا.
The resort has just opened.
لقد تم افتتاح المنتجع للتو.
It can't do without you.
لا يمكن الاستغناء عنك.
You can get me
يمكنك الحصول علي
out of jail.
خارج السجن.
I wouldn't be able to do anything
لن أكون قادرا على فعل أي شيء
if you were jailed.
إذا تم سجنك.
Chengyu.
تشنغيو.
I'll wait for you.
سأنتظرك.
Just catch me!
فقط امسكني!
Prefectural Magistrate.
قاضي المحافظة.
Let's head back too.
دعونا نعود أيضاً
Let's go...
دعنا نذهب...
What was that?
ماذا كان هذا؟
Chengyu.
تشنغيو.
♪If you've never seen a bloom, you can't know hope♪
???إذا لم ترى زهرة أبدًا، فلن تعرف الأمل؟؟؟
♪If you weren't here, I wouldn't have come♪
???لو لم تكن هنا لما أتيت؟؟؟
♪On a soda-lit night, only the wind knows my love♪
في ليلة مليئة بالصودا، فقط الريح تعرف حبي؟؟؟
♪It's a helpless kind of feeling♪
"إنه شعور بالعجز"
♪Like a feather of morning love falling into the deep sea♪
مثل ريشة حب الصباح تسقط في البحر العميق
♪Being unnoticed, yet I still tell you I love you♪
???لم ألاحظك، ومع ذلك مازلت أخبرك أنني أحبك؟؟؟
♪But my confession is drowned out by the wind♪
???ولكن اعترافي غرق في الريح؟؟؟
♪You can't hear it♪
???لا يمكنك سماعه؟؟؟
♪I also want to rush forward♪
???أريد أيضًا أن أسرع للأمام؟؟؟
♪To give you all my heart♪
???لأعطيك كل قلبي؟؟؟
♪Yet it's pushed away by you♪
???ومع ذلك يتم دفعها بعيدا عنك؟؟؟
♪Whether love is spoken or left unspoken♪
???هل الحب يُقال أم يُترك دون أن يُقال؟؟؟
♪I know you understand♪
???أعلم أنك تفهم؟؟؟
♪It's just an accident♪
???إنه مجرد حادث؟؟؟
♪You longed to wander once more, by my side through the throng♪
???هل تمنيت أن تتجول مرة أخرى بجانبي وسط الزحام؟؟؟
♪I know you weren't really here for me♪
???أعلم أنك لم تكن هنا من أجلي حقًا؟؟؟
♪Yet still, who else could bring a surprise quite like you♪
ومع ذلك، من غيرك يمكنه أن يفاجئك بمفاجأة مثلك؟
♪After you left, I didn't want to let go♪
???بعد رحيلك لم اكن اريد ان اتركك؟؟؟
♪You brushed past me, leaving your trace in the crowd♪
???لقد مررت بجانبي، تاركًا أثرك في الحشد ???
♪I didn't shut you out♪
???لم امنعك من ذلك؟؟؟
♪But I couldn't wait for you to stop♪
???ولكنني لم أستطع الانتظار حتى تتوقف؟؟؟
♪Yet I seem to clutch you, unable to let you fade into the crowd♪
ومع ذلك يبدو أنني أتمسك بك، غير قادر على تركك تتلاشى في الحشد؟؟؟